Preliminary Guide to the Frank Bardacke Papers M2014
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 4: Research Files
  - Subseries 4.6: Clippings; Miscellaneous Publications; Print Materials; etc.
    - Coronado, III (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - [Cibbons] Files, III (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Braceros, III (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Cultural Membership, III (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - [Calideu Label Wister], III (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Teamster, III (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Notes, III (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - UPWA, III (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Mohn Interview, III (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Temster/Antle, III (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Walsh Critiques [JLP], III (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Temsters/Craypo, III (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Accounts, III (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Valley Labor Citizen, III (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Southern California Temster, III (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Doc Project, IV (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Doc Project No Feb 7, 1979, IV (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Chatfields/Documentation, IV (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Colton:ALRA Negot, IV (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - DF Files, IV (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Student Information, IV (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - 10/14/74 6/13/75 2/16/76 NEB Board Meetings 1/15/76, IV (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Violence in '73, IV (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Mojica - DS Notes, Time, IV (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Digiorgio Campaign, IIIA (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Chronologies, IIIA (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Henry Anderson, 8 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Labor Organization Annual Report, 11 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Labor Organization Annual Report, 11 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Various Newspapers, 13 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - La Huelga de la Uva, 17 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Where our Food Comes From, 18 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Changes from One Year Ago, 18 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Coastal Growers Assocation, 18 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Case Studies and Research Reports, 18 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Agrarian Advocate Newspaper, 18 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 18 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - D. Company Web Site, 18 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - The California Farm Labor Force Overview and Trends from the National Agricultural Workers Surveys, 18 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - University of Chicago Library, 18 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - A Dissertation submitted in Partial Satisfaction of the requirements for a degree of Doctor of Philosophy in Sociology by Satish Deshpande, 18 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - [State with Interview 2004], 18 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 18 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Coachella Valley's Golden Years, 18 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Union de Campesinos de America AFL-CIO, 18 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Seafarers International Union, 18 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Calla Brand, 18 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Monterey County Annual Crop Report 1969, 18 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Monterey County Annual Crop Report 1968, 18 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Santa Cruz County Annual Crop Report 1984, 18 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Santa Cruz County Annual Crop Report 1985, 18 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Santa Cruz County Annual Crop Report 1986, 18 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - County of Santa Cruz, 18 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - 1986 Agricultural Crop Report, 18 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Santa Cruz County 1987 Crop Report, 18 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Crop Report 1991 Santa Cruz County California, 18 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - Santa Cruz County Trend of Values in Production, 18 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Farmland Acreage, 18 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Agrarian Advocate, 18 (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Pajaro Valley Annual Crop Report 1992, 18 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Strawberry Production and Costs in the Central Coast of California, 18 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Santa Cruz County agricultural Crop Report 1979, 18 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - 1977 Agricultural Crop Report, 18 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Crop Report 1992 Santa Cruz County California, 18 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Santa Cruz County Crop Report 1988, 18 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Pajaro Valley Report of Agricultural Production 1988, 18 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 18 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Annual Crop Report 1971, 1972, 18 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Agricultural Crop Report 1973, 1975, 1978, 18 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Agricultural Crop Report 1980, 1982, 1983, 18 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Notes, 19 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Prologue: The Fast, 19 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Apples, 22 (Box 34, Folder 61)
    - Corporate Farming, 22 (Box 34, Folder 62)
    - Satish Deshpande March 1991 dissertation, 22 (Box 34, Folder 63)
    - Various Articles, 22 (Box 34, Folder 64)
    - AG Mechanization, 22 (Box 34, Folder 65)
    - The Political Economy of Agriculture and Food Systems of Advanced Capitalism, 22 (Box 34, Folder 66)
    - Lettuce, 22 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Rewt, Tak, Land Valve, 22 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Legislation, 22 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Land Reform and Co-operatives, 22 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Export Questions Tomatoes Apples, 22 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Marketing and Retailing, 22 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Various Notes, 22 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Social Sleepwalkers, 22 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Jo Claire Schieffer, 22 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Scientific American September 1976, 22 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Various Articles, 22 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Various Newspapers, 22 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 22 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 22 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - NY Times Feb. 7, 1979, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - News Clipping, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Oxnard Citrus 1978 News Clips, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - July 75 - Aug. 76 (incomplete), Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Fresno Bee 9/9/73 #s of Illegals, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - California Farmer, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Cal. Farmer 1975-77, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Malcriado, Sept. 1-1970 to Oct. 13 '72, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Malcriado Last Issue, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Report July - Aug, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Bakersfield Cal 1971-72, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Living with The Law, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - The Unexpected Aftermath July 1975 to March 1977, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Good, Bad, Unlikely Notes, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - The Good, The Bad, The Unlikely, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - The Good, The Bad, and Victory in Hand, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Outline, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Ganz Attempt, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Civil War, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Civil War, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Living with The Law, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Meanwhile in the Farm, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Victory at Hand, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Fall '79 Winter '80, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Victory in Hand, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Victory in Hand, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Crop Stats, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Thomes/Random Notes, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - File Surfing!, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Lettuce Stats, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Wages for Bob Palin, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Mechanical Grape Harvesting, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Alex and Table, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Stomping out the Vintage 1973, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Victory in Hand, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - The Grand Concession, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - The Grand Concession, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - The Grand Concession, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Grand Concession 2, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - The Grand Concession, Black Cabinet top shelf (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - 2nd Grape Boycott '89, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Alan Rudy, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Alan Rudy, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Rudy 1930s Stuff, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Wobbly Magonistas, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - The Manong, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - INS and Illegals 1979, 24 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Verla Journal, 24 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - 79 North, 24 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - The Last Great Strike, 24 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - The Last Great Strike, 24 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - The Last Great Strike, 24 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Contracts and Field Offices 1978, 24 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Pledge of Silence, 24 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - UFW Contracts 1977, 24 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Contracts 9/76, 24 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - La Paz Community, 24 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Letters of Complaints over illegal Campaign and Responses, 24 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Notes/Articles INS/Braceros, 24 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - UFW and Illegals 71 and 72, 24 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Illegals, 24 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Closing the Boycott 6/78, 24 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Staff List Feb 3, 1977, 24 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Ending the Boycott 1978, 24 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Arizona Farm Workers 1979, 24 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Clinics, 24 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - [Imutan on Pinoys] 78, 24 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Gaurdian Dec. 4, 1977 Purges, 24 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Gaurdian Feb. 78 Boycott ends, 24 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Yates, Nation 77, 24 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Lolschult Dietrich 77-78, 24 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Questions, 24 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - [M...] Incident, 24 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - FW Certifications 1/30/76, 24 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Sam and Union Plans, 24 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Cesar Crazy, 24 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Cesar as Curandero, 24 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Sun Harvest Union 78, 24 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Complaint from Worker about Denny 12/23/77, 24 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Locals, 24 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Trial Procedures, 24 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - ATA - UFW 1976, 24 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Reason 1979, 24 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Reason on CC UFW Answer, 24 (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - CC "Charlatan", 24 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - Complaint to Cesar about/from Staff 3/78, 24 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - Delano Child Care Firings 3/77, 24 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - Duty to Bargain in Good Faith, 24 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - Defending Illegal 78, 24 (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - UFW Philosophy 11/7/77, 24 (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - Agbayani Village, 24 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - Vacations 3/78, 24 (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - [Unemployment/Valientes Peru, 24 (Box 49, Folder 47)
    - Cesar: Penthouse Line, 24 (Box 49, Folder 48)
    - Cesar's altery 9-12/78, 24 (Box 49, Folder 49)
    - S. Nathan on Decerts 8/78, 24 (Box 49, Folder 50)
    - Delano 6, 24 (Box 49, Folder 51)
    - Cesar Defeats Church 1/13/79, 24 (Box 49, Folder 52)
    - 1977 Portion on Immigration Law, 24 (Box 49, Folder 53)
    - Herbert Perry ALRB 1980, 24 (Box 49, Folder 54)
    - To Do, 24 (Box 49, Folder 55)
    - Legislation, 24 (Box 49, Folder 56)
    - [Drunk Bryan] on Purges, 24 (Box 49, Folder 57)
    - Post ALRD Election Campaigns, 24 (Box 49, Folder 58)
    - Cesar's '77 Land Project, 24 (Box 49, Folder 59)
    - Synanon/Delancy, 24 (Box 49, Folder 60)
    - "The Game", 24 (Box 49, Folder 61)
    - Purges, Msc. 77, 24 (Box 49, Folder 62)
    - Frames Sivak/Childcare 2/21/77, 24 (Box 49, Folder 63)
    - Adain the Massacre 4/7/77, 24 (Box 49, Folder 64)
    - Explanation of Monday Night and Letters Massacre and Affair, 24 (Box 49, Folder 65)
    - Memo - Cesar to NEB Carry Out Order, 24 (Box 49, Folder 66)
    - [Gamamma] Election 1977, 24 (Box 49, Folder 67)
    - Analysis of Gumamma Loss 10-6-77, 24 (Box 49, Folder 68)
    - 2nd Wave of Elections, 24 (Box 49, Folder 69)
    - Dept Helmet 9/14/76, 24 (Box 49, Folder 70)
    - Escalante on Coachella 77 Elections, 24 (Box 49, Folder 71)
    - Winning .../Losing Illegals, 24 (Box 49, Folder 72)
    - Cohen Report 6/18/79, 24 (Box 49, Folder 73)
    - WKY June 11/79, 24 (Box 49, Folder 74)
    - Grower Analysis Bispo, 24 (Box 49, Folder 75)
    - Two Startling Facts, 24 (Box 49, Folder 76)
    - 79 Misc., 24 (Box 49, Folder 77)
    - Mojica Firebomb 79, 24 (Box 49, Folder 78)
    - 1979 UFW Strike, 24 (Box 49, Folder 79)
    - Philippene Trip, 24 (Box 49, Folder 80)
    - Border Blues, 24 (Box 49, Folder 81)
    - Interview Denials, 24 (Box 49, Folder 82)
    - Anne Loftis Letter to Me, 24 (Box 49, Folder 83)
    - Malh. N. Yorker Profile, 24 (Box 49, Folder 84)
    - Acuna Letter, 24 (Box 49, Folder 85)
    - Movement vs. Union, 24 (Box 49, Folder 86)
    - Migrant Mother, 24 (Box 49, Folder 87)
    - 1973-74 Overview, 24 (Box 49, Folder 88)
    - 1973 Grape Strikes, 24 (Box 49, Folder 89)
    - Letter to Susan, 24 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Opwn War 1973, 24 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Misc., 24 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Western Lettuce Industry, 24 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Mike Stourn Watson, 24 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Antonio Guevara/Watson, 24 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - [Devedros, 24 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - ]Don Watson Opuna Notes, 24 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Watson 1970 Misc., 24 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Early Book Proposals, 24 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Time Limes, 24 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Random, 24 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Random Notes, 24 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Gresham Andrews, 24 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Epitomoya, 24 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Chavez Misc., 24 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Part 5 Division and Defect (1975-1985), 25 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Prelude, 25 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Dimensions of Democracy, 25 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Fragments, 25 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Picking A Living G.F. Mireles (2005, 25 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Bob Downing, 25 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Letter to Cesar from Stockton, 25 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Requests to Go Home on Xmas, 25 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Porterville Rentals, 25 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Schey on Immigration Law, 25 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Reuther, 25 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - State of Washington Organizing, 25 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Closing the Boycott 1978, 25 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Gallo Boycott, 25 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Mohn's History, 25 (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Legal Dept 1972 1972, 25 (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Inter Harvest - United Brands, 25 (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Donations (Union), 25 (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - Mike Johnson, 25 (Box 50, Folder 35)
    - CC to Ann Others Rude, 25 (Box 50, Folder 36)
    - OP Murphy, 25 (Box 50, Folder 37)
    - Dissort/Union Democracy, 25 (Box 50, Folder 38)
    - Walsh Craypo: "Teamsters" Defeat in Farmworker Organizing", 25 (Box 50, Folder 39)
    - Krissman, Teamos and UFW, 25 (Box 50, Folder 40)
    - Teamos 1976, 25 (Box 50, Folder 41)
    - Fred Ross, 25 (Box 50, Folder 42)
    - 1977 Teamos Agreement, 25 (Box 50, Folder 43)
    - UFW - Teamos Pact 3/21/77, 25 (Box 50, Folder 44)
    - Original 1965 articles 1976, 25 (Box 50, Folder 45)
    - Teamsters, 25 (Box 50, Folder 46)
    - Teamos in Fields, 25 (Box 50, Folder 47)
    - Teamsters, 25 (Box 50, Folder 48)
    - Teamsters, 25 (Box 50, Folder 49)
    - Team Misc., 25 (Box 50, Folder 50)
    - Violence, 1970, 25 (Box 50, Folder 51)
    - Manuel and Richard Misc., 25 (Box 50, Folder 52)
    - Plan I Plan II, 25 (Box 50, Folder 53)
    - "Wall is Black" Meta Medez-Reyes, 25 (Box 50, Folder 54)
    - Advincula Trial, 25 (Box 50, Folder 55)
    - 77 Convention, 25 (Box 50, Folder 56)
    - CC Notes on Marshall 2-3/78, 25 (Box 50, Folder 57)
    - Community Life at La Paz 1/1/78, 25 (Box 50, Folder 58)
    - CC "Union Business and Purpose" 7/77, 25 (Box 50, Folder 59)
    - Wayne State 77 Convention Letter, 25 (Box 50, Folder 60)
    - Budget Forecast Jul. 1,77 - Sept. 30, 77, 25 (Box 50, Folder 61)
    - March 77 NFWSC Meet, 25 (Box 50, Folder 62)
    - Pension Plan, 25 (Box 50, Folder 63)
    - UFW Business, 25 (Box 50, Folder 64)
    - Staff Ruston 3/79, 25 (Box 50, Folder 65)
    - La Paz Memos on Finances, 25 (Box 50, Folder 66)
    - Worker Samp and Poem, 25 (Box 50, Folder 67)
    - Pesticide Campaign, 25 (Box 50, Folder 68)
    - Outline and Twin Line, 25 (Box 50, Folder 69)
    - 70 Lettuce Strike and Boycott, 25 (Box 50, Folder 70)
    - Grower State Tactics 1970, 25 (Box 50, Folder 71)
    - Violence in '70 Strike, 25 (Box 50, Folder 72)
    - Hartmire on '70 Lettuce Strike '72, 25 (Box 50, Folder 73)
    - 1970 Letter Strike and Eamor, 25 (Box 50, Folder 74)
    - Fred Ross, 25 (Box 50, Folder 75)
    - Oral History Antonia w Saldana, 25 (Box 50, Folder 76)
    - Mamih Salvado, 25 (Box 50, Folder 77)
    - Lupe, Sanchez, 25 (Box 50, Folder 78)
    - Maribel Gonzalez, 25 (Box 50, Folder 79)
    - Marian Steig, 25 (Box 50, Folder 80)
    - Juan Soria, 25 (Box 50, Folder 81)
    - Bob Thompson, 25 (Box 50, Folder 82)
    - Luis Torrez, Telephone Interview, 25 (Box 50, Folder 83)
    - Ricardo Villalpando/Watson, 25 (Box 50, Folder 84)
    - Don Vallejo, 25 (Box 50, Folder 85)
    - Watson, 25 (Box 50, Folder 86)
    - Luis Valdez, 25 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Yett et al, 25 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Final - World Hist, 25 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Munoz, Carlos, 25 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Claire Murphy, 25 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Sandy Nathan, 25 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Lauro Navarro, 25 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Bruce Neuberger, 25 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Forest Nixon, 25 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Bob Nunez, 25 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Orendain, 25 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Padilla and Mojica, 25 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Gilbert Padilla, 25 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Padilla Telephone, 25 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Padilla, 25 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Bob Pepper, 25 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Pilar Pederson, 25 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Chayo Pelayo, 25 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Rigoberto Perez, 25 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Bill Ramsey, 25 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Quigley, 25 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Jose Reutema, 25 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Indy Reyes, 26 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Ell Risco, 26 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Al Rojas, 26 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Norverto Romero/Watson, 26 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Fred Ross/Watson, 26 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Untitled Folder, 26 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Chavez Day, 26 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Boycott #s 7/14/76, 26 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Datz/Media Nov 1976, 26 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Nick and Virgina Letter of Complaint, 26 (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - 1976 - Top/Down Hierarchy, 26 (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - Field office Report 6/11/76, 26 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Carlos Carlson Malcriado editor, 26 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Farm Labor Law, 26 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Chavez and Hayson, 26 (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - NSA Support '75, 26 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Jerry Brown, 26 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Villargo on ALRB, 26 (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Fisher, Ghahi, 26 (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - Black and United Front, 26 (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - History of Salinas Valley, 26 (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - Imperial Valley 60-61 Time Mag, 26 (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - NFWA First Election Results Poultry Grant NFWA Statement of Purpose, 26 (Box 51, Folder 45)
    - Pfeffer Insurent Sociologist, 26 (Box 51, Folder 46)
    - Labor Deposits in Ag 1960 Calif. Emp. Dept., 26 (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - SDS 1966, 26 (Box 51, Folder 48)
    - SDS on Early NFWA, 26 (Box 51, Folder 49)
    - Bracero State, 26 (Box 51, Folder 50)
    - Lowente 1939, 26 (Box 51, Folder 51)
    - Straw Strike '74, 26 (Box 51, Folder 52)
    - 1974 Strike Report!! Summarys, 26 (Box 51, Folder 53)
    - Legal Staff Report on '74 Strikes, 26 (Box 51, Folder 54)
    - 74 Asparagus Strike, 26 (Box 51, Folder 55)
    - Santa Paula Lemon Strike '74, 26 (Box 51, Folder 56)
    - Meany Pres. Conference 1973, 26 (Box 51, Folder 57)
    - Boycott Report 1974 Eliseo Medina, 26 (Box 51, Folder 58)
    - Distribution of Staff in 1974, 26 (Box 51, Folder 59)
    - Is on Fresno/Other Left criticism, 26 (Box 51, Folder 60)
    - Sata Paula Strike 1974, 26 (Box 51, Folder 61)
    - AFLCO - UFW Negotiations 1974, 26 (Box 51, Folder 62)
    - Phillip on Hiring Hall 1974, 26 (Box 51, Folder 63)
    - 74 Tomato Strikes Yoco Country, 26 (Box 51, Folder 64)
    - 1974 Strike, 26 (Box 51, Folder 65)
    - Buak, 26 (Box 51, Folder 66)
    - Musitroon Strike 1974, 26 (Box 51, Folder 67)
    - 74 Stockton Tomato Strike Stockton Record, 26 (Box 51, Folder 68)
    - FMN's Convention, 26 (Box 51, Folder 69)
    - Prop 14, 26 (Box 51, Folder 70)
    - Moe Jordain, 26 (Box 51, Folder 71)
    - West Article '84, 26 (Box 51, Folder 72)
    - Friedland - Grapes, 26 (Box 51, Folder 73)
    - Untitled Folder, 26 (Box 51, Folder 74)
    - Cursi, George, 26 (Box 51, Folder 75)
    - Vista, 26 (Box 51, Folder 76)
    - Joe Smith and Board Fall 76, 26 (Box 51, Folder 77)
    - Steve Rivers, 26 (Box 51, Folder 78)
    - Victory in Salinas/Defeat in... Purge, 26 (Box 51, Folder 79)
    - "Chicano Disillusion" with Cesar 1976, 26 (Box 51, Folder 80)
    - Marshall on Prop 14/Leroy D., 26 (Box 51, Folder 81)
    - 1976 Endorsing Convention: "Who is in the Union", 26 (Box 51, Folder 82)
    - Prop 14 Defeat and Purge, 26 (Box 51, Folder 83)
    - Post Prop 14 Purge, 26 (Box 51, Folder 84)
    - 1976 Endorsing 12/28/76 Org Meetg Convention Eliseo - Ranch Comittees, 26 (Box 51, Folder 85)
    - Friedland: Articles, 26 (Box 51, Folder 86)
    - 1975 Convention, 26 (Box 51, Folder 87)
    - UFW ALRA Victory Loaflets, 26 (Box 51, Folder 88)
    - Misc. 75 Elections, 26 (Box 51, Folder 89)
    - [Sweetheart] Elections UFW Workers 16 of 22, 26 (Box 51, Folder 90)
    - White Paper on ALRB, 26 (Box 51, Folder 91)
    - 75-76 Elections/People, 26 (Box 51, Folder 92)
    - Post ALRB Elections, 26 (Box 51, Folder 93)
    - Prop 14 /Brown Telephone, 26 (Box 51, Folder 94)
    - ALRB Analysis 1975-77, 26 (Box 51, Folder 95)
    - AIFLD/Visitors, 26 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Wayne State, 26 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Reuther 05 (unfiled), 26 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Wayne State Archives, 26 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Wayne Archives/2003, 26 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Herrera, 26 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Broyles-Gonzalez Election, 26 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - UFW Criticism, 26 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Majica/ Wages Between '48-'59, 26 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Rufino Contracts, 26 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Audrea, 26 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Labor Dept. Softball Game, 26 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - 4/12/74 Tapes to be destroyed, 26 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Cursillo/Keith Warner, 26 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Back Pain, 26 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Miriam Revions, 26 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Original Proposal, 26 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Me and Joann, 26 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Lowy File, 26 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Cesar Nov. 1973, 26 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Sara Bershtel, 26 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Gallo 2003 Worker UFW, 26 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Alberto Escalante, 26 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - [Dates M...], 26 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Critiques, 26 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Agriculture - UFW Writings, 26 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Political Contributions, 26 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - La Paz Meeting "Union Politics" 6/6/81 Reporter Center org May 24, 1981, 26 (Box 52, Folder 28)